Heiko Oberman Papers 1949-2016 (bulk 1985-2001)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Travel Files, Lectures and Events, 1964-2000; Series II
  - Travel Files, 1964-2000; Subseries 1
    - Calvin conference, cancelled, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Renaissance Conference of Southern California, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - European summer travels, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - The Van Leer Jerusalem Institute, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Ockam/Occam lecture notes, Oxford and St. Louis, 1985-1988 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Medieval Academy meeting, Albuquerque, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - European summer travels, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Pisa, Italy, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Meeting with Secretary of Education of the Netherlands, Amsterdam, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - American Society for Reformation Research, Kalamazoo, 1986, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Dordt College, Sioux Center, Iowa, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Luther Northwestern Theological Seminary, convocation, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - European summer travel, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Devotio Moderna, Zwolle, cancelled, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Cities and their Cultures in Age of Renaissance and Reformation, Harvard, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - German Historical Institute, Washington, D. C., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Kessel Ordination, Berkeley, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Loyola, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - WA Kommission, Tübingen, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Renaissance Society of America, Tempe, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - 16th Century Studies conference, Calvin, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - American Society of Church History, lecture, Lancaster, PA, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - European summer travels, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Luther seminar, Victoria University, University of Toronto, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1989, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Wessel Gansfort and Northern Humanism, Netherlands, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Lecture, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Multiple Voices of the Reformation, Bethel/Newton, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - European summer travels, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Luther lecture, York College, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - International Congress on Calvin Research, Grand Rapids, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Summer travel, Nancy O’Neill visit, Montana, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - European summer travel, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Reformation in Germany and Europe, Washington, D. C., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - American Society of Church History, NYC, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Medieval Heritage and Modern Realities in Jewish-Christian Relations, Auburn, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Conference on Jewish-Christian Dialogue in the Renaissance, Chicago, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Haskins Medal, Medieval Academy of America, Vancouver, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Sixteenth Century Studies Conference, Philadelphia, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Guest lecture, Northern Rockies Institute of Theology, Montana, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Board meeting, Meeter Center-Calvin Studies, St. Paul, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Western Center, American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Los Angeles, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - TARF meeting, cancelled, Gorlitz, Germany, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Reimbursements, summer travel, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - All Souls, Oxford, summer travel, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Presentation, Locher birthday, Bern Switzerland, summer travel, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Guest Professor lecture series, University of South Africa, Pretoria University, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - History of Anti-Semitism, American Academy of Arts and Sciences, UCLA, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - International Congress on Medieval Studies, Kalamazoo, summer travel, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Pforzheim, summer travel, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Conduct service, Okkenbroek, Holland, summer travel, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Zwolle, Netherlands, summer travel, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Ignatius and Luther, epilogue to conference, Bilbao, Spain, summer travel, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - German Historical Institute, cancelled, UCLA, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - American Academy of Arts and Science, cancelled, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Conference, Medieval Academy, cancelled, Princeton, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Visiting fellow, Glendale Community College, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Calvin lectures, Western Theological Seminary, Holland and Michigan, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Medieval Academy, cancelled, Columbus, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Institute for Christian Studies, Geo. Vandervelde, cancelled, Chicago, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Colloquium, Calvin Studies, Davidson College, North Carolina, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - European summer travels, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Western Center, American Academy of Arts and Sciences, cancelled, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - International Congress on Medieval Studies, double session, Kalamazoo, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Periodization- Old Paradigms and New Perspectives, Jerusalem, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Award, Humanities Seminar, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - CHI RHO lecture series, Eugene, OR, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Sixteenth Century Studies conference, Atlanta, cancelled, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Board meeting, Meeter Center for Calvin Studies, Grand Rapids, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Newcombe lectureship, Winnipeg, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Dag Van De Biografie, cancelled, Amsterdam, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Visiting lecture, Tom Brady, UC Berkeley, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Sixteenth Century Studies, St. Louis, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Governing board meeting, Meeter Center, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Liberty Fund Symposium, Brigham Young University, cancelled, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Jan Hus, Bayreuth, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Tjaard Hommes, Maine, cancelled, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Jews and Judaism in Medieval Christian Thought, Wolfenbutte, cancelled, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Calvin Studies Society, Princeton, NJ, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Luther Forschungs Kongress, St. Paul, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Summer travel, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - 250th Anniversary Meeting, American Philosophical Society, Philadelphia, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Christus Theological Institution, Mobile, AL, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Institute for Christian Studies, Toronto, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Ecumenical Gathering of Churches, Pastor Jerry Haas, cancelled, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Holten, Netherlands, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Sixteenth Century Studies conference, Toronto, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Scott Hendrix installation, Gettysburg Lutheran Seminary, cancelled, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Summer travel, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - 30th Anniversary of Institute in Zurich, Prof. Alfred Schindler, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - 29th Congress on Medieval Studies, Grand Rapids, Kalamazoo, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - J. Pelikan’s 70th birthday, Beinecke Library, cancelled, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Medieval Academy, Nominating Committee, Tennessee, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Weinstein Exhibit, Bridwell Library, Dallas, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Colloquium on Calvin, Davidson College, cancelled, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Lutheran Bible Institute, Anaheim, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Fuller Theological Seminary, cancelled, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Netherlands, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Guest lecture, Knox College, Toronto, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Institute for Calvinistic Studies, Seoul, Korea, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Luther, Erasmus and Calvin, Bethany Lutheran College, Minnesota, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Tolerance and Intolerance, Corpus Christi College, Cambridge, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Balke Festrede, Zeist, Netherlands, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Calvin et ses Contemporains, Paris, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Summer travel, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Estates and Societies in Early Modern Central Europe, NYC, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Lecture, Claremont, CA, cancelled, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - William Birkett Williams memorial lecture, Fairmont Church, Ohio, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Summer travel, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Copernican Revolution conference, cancelled, Netherlands, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Theologisches Konvikt, Berlin, cancelled, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Public lecture, Humboldt University, cancelled, Berlin, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Institute for Advanced Studies, cancelled, Jerusalem, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Bridwell Library, cancelled, Dallas, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Luther Colloquium, Gettysburg, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Pacific Lutheran Presbyterian, Timothy Lull, Berkeley, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Concordia and King of Glory, cancelled, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Sixteenth Century Studies conference, Atlanta, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Lecture, UC Berkeley, Tom Brady, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - F. G. W. Schouten, Utrecht, cancelled, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Western Jewish Studies Association, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Summer travel, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Sixteenth Century Studies conference, Toronto, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Summer travel, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Meeter Center, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - 33rd International Congress on Medieval Studies, Kalamazoo, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Leith lectures, cancelled, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Belgun lecture, Thousand Oaks, CA, cancelled, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - American Society of Church History, San Diego, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - American Society of Church History, Washington, D. C., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - 34th International Congress on Medieval Studies, Kalamazoo, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Erasmus Society, Netherlands, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Luther, CNN Interactive, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Heritage lecture, Beeson Divinity School, Samford University, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Sixteenth Century Studies Conference, St. Louis, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Eurasia and Africa during the Last Thousand Years, Madison, WI, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Folger conference, John Pocock, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Summer travel, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - The Long Fifteenth Century, Histrorisches Kolleg, Thomas Brady, cancelled, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Guest lecture, University of Bern, cancelled, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - European Tours (cruises), 1999, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Honorary Dr. of Letters, Valparaiso University, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Luther conference, Trent, Italy, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Summer travel, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Eden Seminary, St. Louis, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Brad Gregory, campus visit, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Taiwan Theological College, cancelled, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Westminster, cancelled, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - UC San Diego Colloquium, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Lectures, Events and Sermons, 1973-2000; Subseries 2
    Public lectures and sermons, notes and full drafts, title of talk or sermon, location, and date labeled on most folders, organized chronologically.
    - The Relation of Medieval and Reformation Thought, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Lecture notes, Karlstadt, Germany, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Sermons, 1973-1983 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Koninklijke Academie, lecture, Dutch, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Lecture, Amsterdam, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Reformation as Decisive Chapter, Oberlin, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Sternstunden der Christenheit, lecture notes (German), 1980 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Luther lectures, 1980-1991 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Frontlines in Luther Research, circa 1983 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - The Amazing Gap, Ascension Lutheran Church, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Vatican II- Hopes, Dreams and Realities, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Antisemitism lectures, 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Antisemitism lectures, (continued), 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - De Erfenis van Calvijn, Kuyper lectures, Amsterdam, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Sermons, sermon notes, quotable quotes, 1986-1999 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Holten, lecture notes, 1986, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Augustine, Eranos, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Leo Braeck Institute and AHA, Washington, D. C., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Conversion in Medieval and Reformation Sources, Brown University, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Luther and the Devil, Gritsch, Gettysburg, PA, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Calvin’s Critique of Calvinism, Lancaster, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - International Congress of Medieval Studies, cancelled, Kalamazoo, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Invitations to conferences/requests for papers, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Theologischen Arbeitskreises fur Reformationsgeschichtliche (TARF), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Europa Afllicta: The Reformation of the Refugees, New York, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Anti-Semitism, Appeasement and All Souls, circa 1990 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - The Riddle of Erasmus, Pretoria, South Africa and Naples, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Guest lecture, sponsored by Dr. Twersky, Harvard University, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Ignatius of Loyola, Bilbao, Spain, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - John Calvin: The Mystery of his Impact, conference in Philadelphia, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Calvin lecture, Secor Dabar, Holten, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Geoffrey Elton Festschrift lecture, Oxford, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Manifest Destiny, Paradiso, Amsterdam and Switzerland, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - The Amazing Gap: Heritage and Preaching in America Today, Ascention Lutheran Church, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Hidden Treasures in John Calvin, Meeter Center, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Between Terror and Tolerance, Prinstesdag, The Hague, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Calvin: Challenge for Modern Theology, the Laidlaw Lectures, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Speech, Dr. Morris Martin’s birthday, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Calvin and Farel, Paris, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Witness to Persecution and Survival (Anne Frank), Jewish Community Center, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Augustine, notes for G. W. Oberman for presentation on Cruise liner, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Luther: The Reformation and Anti-Semitism, Martin Luther Colloquium, Gettysburg, PA, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Tafelrede, Heineken Prize Laureates Dinner, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Lecture, Augustana College, Rock Island, IL, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Quinn Memorial, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Arthur Quinn, Memorial Service, UC Berkeley, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - The Voice of Luthur Today, OSLC and Dove Peace, 1997, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Van Engen Conference, Notre Dame, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - International Congress on Calvin Research, Seoul, Korea, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Cunard lectures, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - From the Last to the Latest Thousand Years, Madison, WI, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - The Lasting Heritage of Calvin, Beeson Divinity School, Alabama and St. Louis, 1999, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - The Future of Ecumenism, St. Cyril’s Church, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Dr. Lewis Spitz, In Memoriam, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - University of Arizona and Tucson Events, 1986-2000; Subseries 3
    Includes project files, correspondence and ephemera related to University of Arizona Department of Late Medieval and Reformation Studies events and community lectures and events in the greater Tucson area. Includes events such as Town and Gown, Summer Lecture Series and Tucson Literary Club. Organized chronologically.
    - Ecumenism, Tucson Ecumenical Council, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Medieval Renaissance and Reformation Committee, 1986-2001 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Annual lecture, Krister and Brita Stendahl, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Lecture, Martin Luther King: Free at Last, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Lectures and sermons, Our Saviour’s Lutheran Church, Tucson, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Summer lecture series, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - David Tracy, fund drive, fellowships for Late Medieval and Reformation Studies Department, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Peter Brown, guest lecture, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - The Mean Student: You Haven’t Got a Prayer, Commencement, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - The Joy of History, President’s Club, luncheon address, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Community Courses, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Humanities Seminar, Europe 1300-1600, 1988, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Town and Gown invitation letters to members of the History Colloquium, formerly Home Study Group, 1988-1999 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Annual Lecture, Martin Marty, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Community Lectures, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - What is History? What is the Historian’s Role? PHI ALPHA THETA, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Sir Geoffrey Elton, visit, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - John D. Kautz, Lutheran Campus Ministry, Tucson, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Rev. Nelson and Rev. Lefebvre meeting, Phoenix, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Preaching in America, Valley Presbyterian Church, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Summer Lecture Series, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Arizona Humanities Council, Summer Lecture Series, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Lutherfest, Fountain of Life Lutheran Church, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Luther lecture, St. Odilia’s Church, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Late Medieval and Early Reformation Department, fundraising diner, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Annual Lecture, Prof. Dr. Rosemary Radford Reuther, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Summer Lecture Series, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Anticlericalism Conference, Tucson, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Opening and closing remarks, Anticlericalism Conference, Tucson, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Conference volume, Anticlericalism Conference, Tucson, 1990-1994 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Conference volume, Anticlericalism Conference, Tucson (continued), 1990-1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - The First Congregational United church of Christ, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Lecture, Norsemen’s Club, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Summer Lecture Series, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Arizona Humanities Council, Summer Lecture Series, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - The Challenge of Martin Luther, Luther Comes to Tucson, Lutheran Campus Ministry Banquet, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Dinner, Mr. William Eerdmans, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Farewell party, Dr. and Mrs. Rublack, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Lutheran Campus Ministry banquet, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Annual Lecture, Desmond Tutu, unable to accept invitation, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Medieval Studies Program Review Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Visitor, Dr. Peter Blickle, cancelled, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - : Legislator’s Day, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Lecture, Dean Smith’s luncheon, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Southwest Regional meeting, American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Tucson, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Luther, Campus Lutheran Ministry, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Annual Meeting, Medieval Academy of America, Tucson, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - The Historian: From Prostitute to Prophet, Humanities Dean Luncheon lecture, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, Erasmus Institute, grant application, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Erasmus Institute, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Weekly speakers, Erasmus Institute, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Tucson Unified School District, Teachers meeting, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Tucson Literary Club, 1994-2002 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Anne Frank in the World, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Visitor, Prof. Dr. F. Higman, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Conference, Christian Kabbalah and European Thought, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - English-Speaking Union, Nina Ruhl, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Ursula Lanis, Memorial Service, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - The Devil and the Devious Historian, SBS lecture and Tucson Literary Club, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Guest lecture, Prof. Susan Karant-Nunn, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - A Conversation and Public Lecture, Calvin, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Honors lunch, W. Dever, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Danforth lectures, Hope College, MI, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Millennium Mileposts, KUAT, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Harvard Alumni Club lecture, Arizona Inn, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Guest Speaker, Dr. Robert Kingdon, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - The First Day Forum, AZ Star and KUAT (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Western Conference on British Studies, Tucson, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Visitor, Prof. Dr. B. Roussel, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Visitor, Dr. A. Pettegree, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Planning, A Symposium: The Work of Heiko A. Oberman, Tucson, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Planning, A Symposium: The Work of Heiko A. Oberman, Tucson (continued), 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Budget, A Symposium: The Work of Heiko A. Oberman, Tucson, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Budget, A Symposium: The Work of Heiko A. Oberman, (continued), 2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Catalina Rotary Club, cancelled, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Dove of Peace Lutheran Church, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Kepler’s Chicken Bone, Tucson Literary Club, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Tucson Literary Club, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Teaching materials, circa 1950-1998; Series III
  Oberman’s lecture notes, syllabi, required readings, bibliographies, publications and class notes. Materials relate to Harvard University, The University of Tübingen and the University of Arizona. Organized chronologically.
  - Luther, course notes, German, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Calvin, Harvard lecture course, 1950s (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Reformation bibliographies, circa 1960-1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Reading lists and bibliographies, 1962-1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Conciliarism, seminar notes, German, 1954-1968 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Syllabae, from many professors, 1965-1997 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Harvard University, reading lists and syllabae, 1968-1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Vrije Universiteit Bibliotheck, correspondence and catalog cards, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - University of Tübingen, Germany, Erasmus course, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Church History 103A, lecture notes, circa 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Reformation bibliographies, circa 1980 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - University of Tübingen, 1980-1983 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Calvin: Leben, Werk und Wirkung, Tübingen seminar, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - History 495G: Forerunners of the Reformation, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - History 696F: Early Modern Europe, Doctoral Seminar, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - History 409: The Reformation, lecture notes, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - History 409, lecture, transparencies, 1985, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - History 409/509, The Reformation, class outline, required reading, 1985-1995 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - History 102: Western Civilization, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - History 409: Reformation, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - History of Christianity, notes, 1987-1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)